

Adam Lehechka

Organized Full-Stack Web Developer offering strong skills in designing, developing, and testing innovative web and mobile applications. Bringing an excellent foundation of academic success and 3+ years of experience within software engineering and DevOps roles.

Experience

R&D Software Engineer / DMSi

Jan. 2020 - Current

Door Configurator and BOM Maintenance

May 2020 – Current

- Leading team of software engineers in development of a door configuration and image generation web application.
- Performing DevOps to create a CI/CD pipeline with Bitbucket, CircleCI, Docker, Google App Engine, Linux, and custom Test Harbor tool.

Building Materials Industry Standard Database

April 2020 – May 2020

• Researched various database solutions for the best option to pursue in the creation of a building materials industry standard database.

Workpoint Integration

Jan. 2020 - April 2020

- Researched the codebase and infrastructure of Workpoint's workflow software
- Discover integration points in plans to integrate the software into DMSi's core products.

Software Development Intern / Union Pacific Railroad

Nov. 2018 - Dec. 2019

Real Estate Management System (REMS)

Sept. 2019 – Current

- Assuming a tech lead role for redesigning a legal document generation system
- Helping to transition legacy system into a modern web application

Revenue Shipment Process (RSP)

Nov. 2018 - Aug. 2019

- Developed 10+ backend microservices utilizing Java, Springboot, and Eclipse
- Responsible for deployment of services to Integrated Cloud Environment
- Designed and developed a highly interactive frontend screen

Education

Bachelor of Science / University of Nebraska - Omaha

Anticipated: Dec. 2020

Majors: Computer Science, Cybersecurity, Management Information Systems

Coursework: Software Engineering, IT Infrastructure, Network Vulnerabilities, Project Management

GPA: 3.5 / 4.0

Personal Project

LockerStock

- Athletic Inventory Management System
- Utilizing Firebase (BaaS) for authentication, hosting, and NoSQL datastore
- Designing frontend with React Typescript, Material-UI, and redux
- CI/CD fully automated using GitHub Actions

Skills

- JavaScript
- React
- Node.js
- PostgreSQL
- HTML/CSS
- DevOps
- Problem Solver
- Quick Learner
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Self-starter